Gyuhyeon Hwang

Software Developer

A junior software developer specializing in Django/Python server-side development. Use C++ and Python as primary languages. Familiar with collaboration and troubleshooting through 2 internships and 6 team project experiences via Git and Slack. I will graduate from university in February 2024.

Contact

Email:

hwgyuhyeon@gmail.com

LinkedIn:

linkedin.com/in/gyuhyeon/

CV:

hgyuhyeon.github.io

Skill

- Python, C++
- Django, DRF
- MySQL, SQLite
- Docker, AWS
- Git, Slack

Education

Department of Computer Science – Chungbuk National University

Bachelor of Science 2019.03 – 2024.02(Expected)

Computer Science – Angelo State University

Study Abroad 2022.01 – 2022.05

Languages

English – Intermediate

Korean - Native

Experience

Software Developer, Internship, 2022.06 – 2022.07

Headstart SV, Seoul, South Korea (Hybrid)

Worked as a Django/Python developer. Develop and deploy a new project with 7 team members. Manage and finalize the team project.

- Build, deploy and manage the server via AWS and docker.
- Implement and test API through Django/Python.
- Apply AI model and React web project made by other teams to the Django server.

Software Developer, Internship, 2021.06 – 2021.07

Flug Mediaworks, Cheongju, South Korea

Worked as a full-stack PHP/JavaScript developer. Implement web pages based on designed drafts and participate in maintenance.

- Implement a web page both front-end (HTML/CSS) and back-end (PHP/JavaScript).
- Translate the Korean web pages to English and implement an English version.
- Fix errors & problems of the web pages on service.

Project

Software Developer, 2023.03 – 2023.10

Picaxer, Graduation Project

- A pixel art editor that can draw, share, and apply pixel art in our games.
- Design and implement database structure via Firebase.
- Connect database and unity project in C# scripts.
- Develop community services API.